oh why hello
we didn't see you coming you showed up
just in time
i was just getting ready to share a
spooky tale from my story collection
Knuckles always tells the best scary
stories
hey how about you come and listen but
only a few got balls of steel
we don't need any babies around here yes
what are you waiting for then [ __ ] pull
up a seat and get comfy
yes
our story takes place in 1976.
a group of archaeologists are on their
way to an expedition in ancient egypt
excited to dig a preluxe of the past
that were lost to the sands of time
one such archaeologist on this trip was
Knuckles the Echidna
he's a veteran in this field and dug up
at least 20 hidden tombs
but he doesn't want any of that no he
has only one goal in mind this time
one that will make him rich as [ __ ] if
he succeeds
his dream is to find a mummy so that he
can sell it on ebay for a million
dollars
but finding a mummy is really hard even
for the best of the best
Knuckles however was ready he brought
his favorite pickaxe
with him on his trip and was ready for
the challenges ahead
or so he thought when the jeep came to a
stop
Knuckles climbed out and looked over the
sandy morning horizon
the air was cool and the sun was just
coming over the dunes
it was beautiful it won't stay like this
for long
Knuckles said the desert is hot as they
[ __ ]
all of the archeologists knew they would
have to work fast before it gets too hot
they met up with the other expedition
team one of them was Knuckles friend
mammoth the Hedgehog he also wanted to
find a mummy
but that can wait for now because for
now they need to dig
outside you see going inside the
pyramids of egypt are illegal without
permission
so Knuckles and mammoth knew they would
have to sneak inside when nobody else
could see them
in the cover of night hey Manic ask
Knuckles
what do you want can't you see I'm
working my butt off over here
Manic replied and indeed he was
Manic was working very very hard so hard
that an ocean of sweat was building
inside of his butt crack
you could even say it was quite possibly
the largest body of water currently
within this oasis of dry sand
the sun is setting when night falls we
put our plant into action the green man
smiled at this
he was so excited to go look for a mummy
all of the archaeologists started
putting up their tents to go to Sleet
but not Knuckles and Manic
they had their own idea of fun Manic
pulled some torches that he was hitting
between his butt crack
they tried to light them on fire but
Manic's sweat made them to damp
so they threw them aside and picked up
different sticks off the floor
and littles instead now they can see
where they're going as they happily go
into one of the pyramids
it wasn't long before they came across
something mysterious
it looked to be made of the finest gold
in the land could it be
could this be what they were searching
for it was without a doubt in their
minds
a sarcophagus Manic gave Knuckles a good
heart smack on the ass
we did that Knuckles Manic said with
this we will become one of the richest
people on the planet
Manic took a step forward trembling with
excitement to see their haul up close
he grabbed the lid of the sarcophagus
and gave it a yank
he was not prepared for what he saw next
it was a mummy all wrapped up in
bandages
but the bandages barely covered anything
at all
of course this was all the better for
Manic this money had big boobies
and a big buttt so Manic slapped that ass
like there was no tomorrow
but when he tried to grab her boobies
the mummy reached out and grabbed him
instead
Knuckles this mummy is going to kill me
you have to do something
anything they both realized now this was
no ordinary mummy
this was the big boob [ __ ] the most
famous queen of egypt
it is said that she [ __ ] over a
million people each day
under her rule of course this was only a
rumor
but neither mana cornicles wanted to
stay to find out
with the war cry Knuckles threw his door
chat the monster
let my friend go use lut he cried out in
anger and then fear
it worked for only a second the mummy
bandage is caught on fire
but because she was wearing barely any
bandages anyway
it only slowed her down enough for Manic
to escape her grasp for a moment
while fleeing from the monster they
heard the strange chant escape her lips
was this a magic spell the mummy's curse
they heard about
oh no it was worse than they could have
possibly imagined
their entire bodies were enveloped in a
light that glowed the same color as
green beans
as they got outside Manic slipped and
fell in a pile of [ __ ]
it seems like one of the archeologists
took a huge [ __ ] dumb here
Knuckles knew exactly what's going on
but he didn't want to tell Manic it
would scare him
they were cursed by the mummy and bad
luck will follow them for
the rest of their lives they could not
kept this to himself
hoping that the slip and poop was only a
mere coincidence
the next day Manic was hot as [ __ ] so he
went to get a drink
of water from the flask that he brought
with him on this trip
however it was empty the water was not
there
as it fit magic leaf and ish 2.
that was two times Manic experience bad
luck and Knuckles knew the third will be
his last
that is the rule of the money's purse
Knuckles tried to warn his friend
but he wasn't having it Manic was
packing his things to leave when out of
nowhere he slipped in another pile of
[ __ ]
falling straight onto his pickaxe Manic
Manic please get up oh God Knuckles yell
but his words could not reach him he was
dead
hold the [ __ ] up what do you mean I'm
dead you made me go out like a [ __ ]
Manic this is my story you want one go
make your own [ __ ]
Knuckles knew what he had to do now he
had to lift this money's curse
all by himself otherwise he will suffer
the same fate
as the green man but how you might ask
yourself
how does one free themselves of this
evil spell well that's a simple question
[ __ ]
you must climb the tallest pyramid in
the whole world
and find the richest sexiest pharaoh in
the land
Bartleby Montclair of Dresden he is the
only one that Knuckles can rely on now
it took the ignorant five days and six
nights to reach the top
and when he did he saw them the pharaoh
Bartleby and his [ __ ]
Sonic the Hedgehog Sonic just got done
sucking his balls
why are you here the beautiful man said
with a voice so warm and soothing
i have been cursed only you have the
power to save me a great one
i beg of you release me from the mummy's
curse so that I don't die
no I gotta say Knuckles this was your
best story yet
hey you agree to don't you I guess
[Music]
[Applause]
you